<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Information Book</string>

    <string name="united_kingdom">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: London\n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t: London\n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: English\n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 242,495 km2\n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: GBP\n\n

        \t\t The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain,is a country in Northwestern Europe, off the north-western coast of the continental mainland.It comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland.It includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and most of the smaller islands within the British Isles. Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland; otherwise, the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea, and the Irish Sea. The total area of the United Kingdom is 94,060 square miles (243,610 km2),with an estimated 2022 population of nearly 67 million people.

\n\n\t\t The United Kingdom has evolved from a series of annexations, unions and separations of constituent countries over several hundred years. The Treaty of Union between the Kingdom of England (which included Wales) and the Kingdom of Scotland in 1707 resulted in their unification to become the Kingdom of Great Britain. Its union in 1801 with the Kingdom of Ireland created the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland. Most of Ireland seceded from the UK in 1922, leaving the present United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, which formally adopted its name in 1927.The nearby Isle of Man, Guernsey and Jersey are not part of the UK, being Crown Dependencies, but the British government is responsible for their defence and international representation.

\n\n\t\t The UK became the first industrialised country and was the world\'s foremost power for the majority of the 19th and early 20th centuries, particularly during the Pax Britannica between 1815 and 1914.The British Empire, at its height in the 1920s, encompassed almost a quarter of the world\'s landmass and population, and was the largest empire in history; however, its involvement in the First World War and the Second World War damaged Britain\'s economic power and a global wave of decolonisation led to the independence of most British colonies.British influence can be observed in the legal and political systems of many of its former colonies, and the UK\'s culture remains globally influential, particularly in language, literature, music and sport. English is the world\'s most widely spoken language and the third-most spoken native language.

\n\n\t\t The United Kingdom is a constitutional monarchy and parliamentary democracy.The capital and largest city of the United Kingdom (as well as the capital of England) is London. The cities of Edinburgh, Cardiff, and Belfast are respectively the national capitals of Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland. Other major cities include Birmingham, Manchester, Glasgow, and Leeds.The UK consists of three distinct legal jurisdictions: England and Wales, Scotland, and Northern Ireland. This is due to these areas retaining their existing legal systems even after joining the UK.Since 1998, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland also have their own devolved governments and legislatures, each with varying powers.


    </string>

    <string name="france">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Paris\n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t: Paris\n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: French\n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 640,679 km2\n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Euro\n\n

        \t\t In the history of France, the First Republic,sometimes referred to in historiography as Revolutionary France, and officially the French Republic was founded on 21 September 1792 during the French Revolution. The First Republic lasted until the declaration of the First Empire on 18 May 1804 under Napoléon Bonaparte, although the form of the government changed several times.
\n\n\t\ This period was characterised by the downfall and abolition of the French monarchy,the establishment of the National Convention and the Reign of Terror, the Thermidorian Reaction and the founding of the Directory, and, finally, the creation of the Consulate and Napoleon\'s rise to power.The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom or Britain,is a country in Northwestern Europe, off the north-western coast of the continental mainland.It comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland.It includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and most of the smaller islands within the British Isles. Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland otherwise, the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea, and the Irish Sea. The total area of the United Kingdom is 94,060 square miles,with an estimated 2022 population of nearly 67 million people.
\n\n\t\t Under the Legislative Assembly, which was in power before the proclamation of the First Republic, France was engaged in war with Prussia and Austria. In July 1792, the Duke of Brunswick, commanding general of the Austro–Prussian Army, issued his Brunswick Manifesto, threatening the destruction of Paris should any harm come to King Louis XVI of France.
\n\n\t\t This foreign threat exacerbated France\'s political turmoil amid the French Revolution and deepened the passion and sense of urgency among the various factions. In the insurrection of 10 August 1792, citizens stormed the Tuileries Palace, killing six hundred of the King\'s Swiss guards and insisting on the removal of the king.
\n\n\t\t A renewed fear of anti-revolutionary action prompted further violence, and in the first week of September 1792, mobs of Parisians broke into the city\'s prisons. They killed over half of the prisoners, including nobles, clergymen, and political prisoners, but also common criminals, such as prostitutes and petty thieves. Many victims were murdered in their cells raped, stabbed, and slashed to death. This became known as the September Massacres.


    </string>

    <string name="italy">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Rome\n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t: Rome\n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: Italian\n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 301,340 km2\n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Euro\n\n

        \t\t Italy is a country in Southern Europe. It is a member of the European Union. Its official name is the Italian Republic. The Italian flag is green, white and red. Italy is a democratic republic.

\n\n\t\t Italy is a founding member of the European Union.In 2022, Italy\'s president is Sergio Mattarella. Its prime minister is Giorgia Meloni. Italy is also a member of the G7, as it has the eighth largest gross domestic product in the world.

\n\n\t\t Italy has become famous for its wine and food. Some foods are different between regions. Famous dishes include various types of pasta, pizza, and grapes. Olives are also often used.

\n\n\t\t Before 1861, Italy was made up of smaller kingdoms and city-states. The country\'s capital, Rome, is one of the most famous cities in the world. It was the capital of the Roman Empire. Other famous cities in Italy include Venice, Naples, Turin, Genoa, Florence, Palermo, and Milan.The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom or Britain,is a country in Northwestern Europe, off the north-western coast of the continental mainland.It comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland.It includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and most of the smaller islands within the British Isles. Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland. otherwise,the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea, and the Irish Sea. The total area of the United Kingdom is 94,060 square miles,with an estimated 2022 population of nearly 67 million people.

\n\n\t\t The Italian peninsula was historically the native place and destination of numerous ancient peoples.The Latin city of Rome in central Italy, founded as a Kingdom, became a Republic that conquered the Mediterranean world and ruled it for centuries as an Empire.With the spread of Christianity, Rome became the seat of the Catholic Church and of the Papacy. During the Early Middle Ages, Italy experienced the fall of the Western Roman Empire and inward migration from Germanic tribes. By the 11th century, Italian city-states and maritime republics expanded, bringing renewed prosperity through commerce and laying the groundwork for modern capitalism.The Italian Renaissance flourished in Florence during the 15th and 16th centuries and spread to the

\n\n\t\t rest of Europe. Italian explorers also discovered new routes to the Far East and the New World, helping to usher in the European Age of Discovery. However, centuries of rivalry and infighting between the Italian city-states among other factors left the peninsula divided into numerous states until the late modern period.During the 17th and 18th centuries, the Italian economic and commercial importance significantly waned.

    </string>

    <string name="taj_mahal">


        \t\t The Taj Mahal is an Islamic religious building, mosque and tomb in India. It was built in the 17th century by Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan in memory of his wife, Mumtaz Mahal. Its chief architect was Ustad Ahmed Lahauri.

\n\n\t\t The building is in the city of Agra, Uttar Pradesh. It is widely thought as one of the most beautiful buildings in the world. It is one of India\'s biggest tourist attractions.

\n\n\t\t The Taj Mahal is listed as a UNESCO World Heritage Site, together with the Agra Fort, 2.5 kilometers away. It was listed as one of the 7 Wonders of the World in 2007. It is on the south bank of the Yamuna river in Agra.

\n\n\t\t The building was originally white. Because of pollution, it is turning yellow. Sulphur dioxide in the atmosphere reacts with water molecules and becomes sulphuric acid, which slowly destroys the outer layer of the building.

\n\n\t\t The Taj Mahal is one of the most notable examples of Islamic architecture ever built. When it was built, most of India was ruled over by the Mughal Empire except the South. Shah Jahan was a Mughal emperor who came into power around 1628. According to historians, Shah Jahan loved building and architecture, which gave him the nickname The Builder Of Marvels. The Taj Mahal was built for Shah Jahan\’s third wife, Mumtaz Mahal meaning the Jewel of the palace. She became ill giving birth to their 14th child. As she was about to die, she asked Shah Jahan to make her the most beautiful tomb that was ever built. She died on 17 June 1631. In 1657, Shah Jahan fell ill. He died in captivity in 1666. His tomb was placed besides Mumtaz Mahal\'s.


    </string>

</resources>